Oh.
December. Christmas was right around the corner.
I got a call from my foster sister, Kyoko.
You forgot something? A watch?
Found it.
Thank goodness. It's a special gift from Gotoh. He gets mad if I don't wear it.
Dammit, Rei. If I catch a cold, it's gonna be all your fault!
I said to wait for me at the McBurger at the station.
No way! That place is way too noisy. Why couldn't we have just gone to your place to meet?
You're asking me why?
How much you wanna bet I can guess what you were thinking, huh, Rei?
I'm just kidding. Don't be so serious.
So, what are you gonna do during the holidays? You're coming home, right?
I can't. I have a lot of matches to get ready for. I need to focus on my training.
That's what you're going with? Don't use your matches as an excuse.
Isn't your last one of the year against Mr. Yasui on the 24th?
Oh, that reminds me. Did you hear what happened?
It seems he and his wife are finally getting divorced.
He's usually a meek guy, but when he loses, he gets plowed and goes out gambling.
I'm surprised his wife has put up with it for so long.
I just can't help but feel sorry for his daughter. It must have been scary for her.
Living under the same roof for the father who becomes a monster every time he loses.
Man, I hate this.
But I hear his daughter had one important wish.
She said she wanted to be with her dad at least until Christmas.
I just can't stand her words.
Doesn't it bring a tear to your eye? It's so sad.
The way she speaks, it sticks to me like glue.
Hey, Rei. Are you listening?
Even more than that.
What's with you?
I hate myself for wanting to hear her.
Your scarf's gonna blow away. You should be more careful how you wear it.
Her and all of her poisonous words.
Children have it rough these days.
They have no choice in who their parents are.
Oh, now that I think of it, that wasn't true in your case.
You were lucky enough to choose your own father.
So you went ahead and chose someone else's.
Whoa!
Dad, can we open them now?
Yeah, sure.
What's with this thing?
A giant teddy bear? Really?
Come on, I'm already in middle school.
I don't play with toys anymore.
Whoa, it's a new game bomb.
For a child of this family, or anyone striving to be a pro, the value of those beautiful shogi pieces, their meaning, the feelings of their father, were all unmistakable.
So what do you think, Ray? Should I have gotten you some toys for Christmas as well?
No. Thank you. It's just what I wanted. I love it, really. It's great.
Their feelings at the moment were obvious.
My foster brother and sister must have been devastated by our father's decision.
Come on. It's sad, don't you think?
A dad who comes home after winning, or a dad who comes home after losing?
So, which is better for a final Christmas memory? A winner or a loser?
Hmm. It looks like aside from music and P.E., you didn't do so bad.
In fact, your grades for math and physics are quite good.
That being said, here. You need to be at Shogi Hall by 9.30, right? Better get moving.
Anyway, you're a busy guy these days. You even have a match right before winter break.
You just barely met the attendance minimum for this term.
You might not be so lucky next term if you have more matches. It'll be tough, so watch out.
Duh! You want me to lose? But I have my livelihood to think of.
By the way, there's a Christmas party today.
Apparently, your classmates are going to be hosting it after the closing ceremony.
Have you heard about it?
Of course not. You know I haven't heard a thing. So I'd rather not know, please.
Well, I guess there's only one thing to do.
After your match, why don't you come back here and hang out?
Just two guys in this crummy room eating cake while playing Shogi.
Suddenly!
I turn around and no one's there!
Wait a second! Now I'm starting to sound like a bitter old teacher!
Oh no! At least stick around and listen until I'm done talking!
Right, Kiriyama?
When did it start to hurt?
When did Christmas become such a painful holiday for me?
I've had this random thought before.
It's just like a report card.
Of the year's worth.
In that one year,
my friends,
my family,
my parents,
was I worthy of their love?
How did I make them feel about me?
Yesui,
Six-Den.
The doors are closing.
Please use caution.
But I hear his daughter had one important wish.
She wanted to be with her dad until Christmas.
A dad who comes home after winning or a dad who comes home after losing?
Well, Ray…
Time to begin.
Let's have a good and fair game.
Do good.
We have an excellent picture but something is the only thing I have for her mom here.
Now we're going back to my bathroom, which takes a long time.
Now we'll enjoy優 dig.
Tambchnet the spirits of a birthday party!
I had an affair too much then….
Thank you.
I lost the match.
Yeah, definitely.
It could have gone that way.
If I'd noticed at the time, that's what I would have done.
But I didn't notice.
So what does it matter now?
It's over and nothing can be done.
I bet you could see all the moves that could have been played, every possibility.
But I didn't see any of it, so what good does that do?
Mr. Yasui continued on like that, muttering to himself.
There was the smell of alcohol in his breath, and it was uncomfortable when he sighed.
The match began slowly.
He started with the castle opening.
Carefully, carefully, from the way he played, I could almost hear him tell himself that.
Don't make a mistake.
However, when we got back from the lunch break, Mr. Yasui made a huge mistake.
It took him a moment, but he noticed it too.
However, if he attacked the king from 8-6 pawn, who knows what would have happened.
If he pulled his knight back and managed to hold out, which side would victory tilt towards?
But then, Mr. Yasui's mood changed.
I could see his strength and confidence fading.
Why?
Hold on.
There are still options he can try.
I hear his daughter had one important wish.
Wait a second.
Why?
I don't get it.
That easily?
You can't let go.
You've got to stay focused.
She said she wanted to be with her dad at least...
Don't give up.
There's too much at stake.
At least until Christmas comes.
Please.
I'm begging you.
Don't let go.
I have to go.
I lost the match.
I think that's enough.
No point in more critiquing.
I think I've had more than enough for today.
Hey, Mr. Yasui!
He's gone.
Where'd he go?
Oh, there he is.
Where's he going?
The station isn't that way.
Mr. Yasui!
Here you go.
That ain't mine.
Sorry.
Here, take it!
All right, shut up already!
Boy, man, this was gonna be our last Christmas together.
Shit!
Blimey.
I don't know.
I can tell you don't practice.
If you say I should but I can't then why don't you just quit?
Don't show.
For me everything is on the line.
I don't know.
I don't even have anything else left.
Damn it.
Shogi's all I've got.
You gotta stop using your alcohol as an escape.
I have no patience for weak players.
If you run away, if you can run away, well then why?
I had once said that I have no reason to fight.
The truth is, I know that a beast lives deep inside of me.
A furious rampaging beast.
It would devour everything in sight just to survive.
When the pieces are lined up across the board, its hand reaches out towards the path of survival.
Even if it means misery for someone else, my future awaits no matter what.
I am known as happiness.
The resurrection has been beyond amusicMuseman.
Part 2 Corinthians 7 concept designer Given his mind.
Jesus Christ said about death.
You need to be vue for potassium.
You need to lead your mind.
Right away.
Used to be due.
But he must save uranium.
You need to build a new month.
Yes, he must savehana Snowys.
Yay! It's Rei's place!
Keep this towel around your neck.
I'll change it if it gets sweaty.
Rei, is that you? Are you alright?
What an idiot.
No, you're wrong. I wanted you to be here.
You're the one who helped me.
Don't miss the next episode of March Comes In Like a Lion!
Be sure to keep an eye out for the big scene between me and Kiriyama!
Uh, the big scene?
The end of the day is the doubt it's wonderful.
Not with her eyes!
She won't do the demons yet.
I live with the old children in the school of the city that attracted them!
That you're right, the air was an assumptive encounter.
We träume and see it was a fun fact!
Easy!